cpmstar.com 2019-04-28

# CPMStar - Privacy Policy

The Oldest and Largest Ad Network in the Games and Youth Oriented Entertainment Space

_Privacy Policy: Effective May 24, 2018_

Tactics Network, LLC and the CPMStar service are committed to protecting customer privacy online. The following privacy policy applies solely to our CPMStar internet advertising services (the "Services") for end users viewing or interacting with advertisements ("you") through our service. Tactics Network LLC may be referred to as the "Data Controller" of data collected through the Services. 

Cookies

When viewing advertisements shown via the CPMStar service, you may receive and transmit web cookies. We use cookie data for a number of important purposes, including but not limited to security purposes such as rate limiting user behaviors from abusing our service by way of clicking or interacting with ads too many times, to enhance the user interface ("UI") and user experience ("UX") purposes, as well as limit the frequency and type of ads showing to a particular user. We may expand our use of cookies to save additional data as new features are added to the Service. If you would not like to receive and transmit such cookies, you may disable cookies for our site or sites in general within your web browser. You may also [click here](http://server.cpmstar.com/optout.aspx) to opt out of tracking cookies. Cookies are pieces of data that sites and services can set on your browser or device that can be read on future visits or during the same session. 

Data We Collect

**Personally Identifiable Information:**  
We do not currently collect personally identifiable information in the process of serving ads to end users. 

**Traffic Information:**  
We or our advertisers may track page or image impression counts by using the information sent to our servers when your browser electronically requests our pages or images. Such information includes, but is not limited to, your Internet Protocol address, information about your web browser such as software make and model, referring link, time of transmission, operating system, window size, and any other information your browser automatically transmits in response to web content. We use this information to limit the advertisements you may see, as well as for security purposes to prevent abuse of the Services. 

**Aggregated Information:**  
We collect data on our users in aggregate form in order to both report on performance of our advertisements to our partners and for billing purposes. In addition, we use this data in order to optimize performance of the advertisements we deliver through the Services. This aggregated data may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and we may share aggregated data with our affiliates, agents, and business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes. 

**Expansion of Services:**  
We may expand our services in the future to collect and use additional informaton. 

Data Retention

We generally retain data from as long as it may be relevant to the purposes identified herein or to serve our legitimate interests. To dispose of data, we may anonymize it, delete it, or take other appropriate steps. Data may persist in copies made for backup and business continuity purposes for additional time. 

Security

We take reasonable steps to protect the information provided via the Services from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet or email transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, email sent to or from the Services may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special case in deciding what information you send to us via email. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any information via the internet. 

Third Party Advertisers

By clicking on an advertisement or viewing a pop up or pop under advertisement, you may be visiting the sites of third party advertisers using the CPMStar service. Tactics Network LLC is not responsible for the content of such sites and can not guarantee that those sites will guard your privacy as strictly as we do. Before entering personally identifiable information into a third party site, we strongly recommend viewing the site's privacy policy and determining how your information will be used. 

Changes to Our Privacy Policy

As our services evolve, this Privacy Policy may be revised to reflect those changes, where applicable. We therefore reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time, for any reason, without prior notice. Notice of such amendments will be posted as an updated Privacy Policy on this website, and an effective date will be indicated. Users are encouraged to check our site frequently to review the current Privacy Policy in effect. 

Contacting Us

Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information practices  
You may contact our Data Protection Officer at 1626 Montana Ave, Suite 204, Santa Monica, CA 90403, or send an email to contact@cpmstar.com.
